This is it. It's gotta be.
What'll it be? We have enough supplies to keep going, but turning back might not be a bad idea.
No. We press on. Everyone, check your gear.
You got it.
Rudy, I have a few extra scrolls here. Would you like some?
Please. I'll take a few healing spells if you don't mind.
Here.
Thank you. This will help.
We don't know what kind of guardian we're going to face in there, but we have more than enough firepower.
And I'll work as hard as I can to support you. You won't even need the scrolls.
Thanks, Roxy. I spook pretty easily, so I'm glad you have my back.
Of course. You can always count on me.
Okay. Are we all good to go?
Hey, Rudy.
What is it?
I hate to say this, especially given what we're about to do here.
Okay, then I don't want you to.
Oh, okay.
I'm not letting him drop any bombshells before the big fight.
I can wait until we get home.
Let's go.
It's a Hydra. I've never seen one before.
Zenith! What's she doing in there?
You dumbass! Don't rush in!
Rear-line firing! Silent Fist of the Frost Giant! Icicle break!
Stop cannon!
Did it deflect this?
On your right!
Rapid dark currents gush forth! Flash run!
Earthen pillar!
Does magic not work on this abomination?
That sound... Is it a force field? Disturb magic? I can't tell. But I can't touch it. What should I do? Just keep trying?
Rudy, see that? It's healing. We should retreat!
You're up!
I'm on it!
No you don't! We gotta fall back!
Get off, Geese, you traitor! Like hell, I'm just gonna turn back now!
Rotinash!
Retreat! To the magic circle!
Let this divine power be rich and nourishing.
Offering those whose strength has been lost, the strength tries again.
Healing.
Are you all right?
Oh, it was only a scratch.
Hey, Dad.
That was her. That was Zenith. It had to be.
Come on. Stay calm.
Yeah, I know. Sorry. I'm all right now.
Do you think Mom is still alive in there?
What?
What difference does it make? We're saving her.
No, you're right.
Enough of that. No infighting.
Rudy, you saw her.
That was Zenith.
That is your mother in there, son.
How can you be so goddamn calm?
Loosing my composure isn't going to solve anything.
That is not the point.
Maybe I am a little lukewarm.
But I don't have much of a relationship with Zenith.
At this point, she's less my mother than someone I used to live with.
I haven't seen her in almost ten years.
I was seven.
Let's regroup.
Make sure we're on the same page.
What?
Our magic had zero effect on that Guardian.
It regenerates rapidly.
It broke through Alina Lisa's defense just by brushing up against her.
And then there's Mom, who's trapped inside a crystal.
And frankly speaking, we don't know if she's alive or dead.
Oh, piss off. I already know all of that.
What I'm saying is that's not the attitude to have when we finally found her.
Knock that off!
You can argue with each other when we're back at the end!
Had enough of this shit.
Get that out of your system?
Because we need to talk this out.
Hey, it's okay.
If you say so.
Paul and I have butted heads before.
Things are just a little out of whack right now.
Intentions are high.
Well, as far as Zenith is concerned, she's not trapped in there forever.
You think?
I've heard the same.
I know of one other person who was in a very similar situation.
And she is very much alive.
But we'll have to defeat that Guardian first.
And I haven't the faintest idea of where to begin.
No kidding.
You can tell by looking it's a Hydra.
But I've never heard of one with skills like that before.
And the cursed thing can heal itself, too.
It's most likely a manatite Hydra.
I've read an account of one before.
An infernal dragon covered in magic stone scales that absorb mana.
I thought it was a fairy tale, but it appears they do exist.
Mana absorption.
So, are you saying that you and I won't be able to damage that thing at all?
Well, if the book I read was telling the truth, then magic might work if you fire point blank.
Still gonna revive itself, so what are we supposed to do about that?
That is a nuisance.
I've heard that if you burn the stump where the head was cut off, it won't be able to regenerate.
At least that's how Heracles did it in Greek mythology.
He lopped off the Hydra's heads one by one and used a torch to cauterize the open wounds so it couldn't heal.
Not that ancient folktales are a particularly credible source.
That's a thought.
Kill the tissue there.
Yeah.
We don't have torches, but it shouldn't be able to deflect magic where it doesn't have scales.
Huh.
I guess it's worth a shot.
Okay.
I'm all in if you guys are.
What do you think?
That work for you, Paul?
Yeah.
You don't sound too enthusiastic.
Weren't you listening?
You're the only one of us who can chop that thing's heads off.
Paul severs the heads, I cauterize the wounds.
And chances are, I'll have to do it at melee range.
Huh.
Alina Lys, Talhand, Geese, Roxy.
You've done so much for me.
You've traveled the world for me, for my family.
Went to lengths I couldn't dream to ask of you.
And this is where it all ends.
We're going to save Zenith.
But even if we can't, at least my family is accounted for.
Please lend me your strength.
This one last time.
How could I say no?
You're acting so humble for once.
Heavens, Paul.
What fool would say no after all of this?
You know you can always count on me.
I'm in.
Let's win this.
We've made it this far because we worked together.
We can't turn back now.
Rudy, my boy.
I'm so lucky to have a son like you.
Come on, Dad.
Lighten up.
You can flatter me after we beat the Hydra.
It's not flattery.
It's true, and I mean it.
I can't keep a cool head like you.
I never could.
I don't come up with grand ideas.
I'm just an idiot who charges in headfirst without thinking.
I'm an awful dad.
You deserve better, Rudy.
I failed you.
With that in mind, I'm going to say this to you.
This is something a parent should never say to their child.
Ready?
Yes.
Save your mother, even if it kills you.
Sir!
Okay.
Let's go.
He's right.
No parent should say that.
But he's not being cruel.
He's showing his conviction.
His trust in me.
I have to honor it.
We're going to save Zenith.
To that end, Paul and I would share the same determination.
Ready?
Let's go!
Yeah, looks like I'll have to get up close after all.
Just as we predicted.
So, can you do it?
I think I can.
Rudy!
Stay right behind me.
This thing is no joke.
Right!
Fight him up!
Who's that?
Yes!
It works!
Atta boy!
Come for me!
I've got you!
Roxy!
Let this divine power be rich and nourishing.
Healing!
Now, son!
Audit!
Move!
It's coming our way!
Let this divine power be rich and nourishing.
Healing!
Many thanks.
Now's our chance.
Let's go, Rudy!
Wait.
Something's not right.
What?
No!
Don't give that thing time to heal!
Get in there now!
Let the great protection of ice crail me at the place thou seekest.
Call forth your glacial torrent here and now!
Ice smash!
Roxy!
May this smoldering spark call forth a great and staring blessing!
Flame Druid!
That can't be good!
Incoming!
It's a breath attack!
Everyone behind me!
No!
Ah!
Workin' on it!
Okay, one more to go.
Focus up!
Look out, Riii!
Watch out!
Riii!
Rox, die!
May this smoldering spark go forth the greatest stirring blessing!
Flamethrower!
All right.
We did it.
Our angel of miracles,
bestow thy heavenly breath unto the beating heart before thee.
O peace!
May your servants blessed be they with sunlight.
Swoop down from their ocean of radiance,
their pure white wings spread wide.
Drive away this blood before thee.
Shine healing!
I did what I could.
The spell isn't strong enough to regrow limbs.
Just stay calm.
I beat a Hydra,
and all I lost was a hand.
If Paul hadn't gotten to me in time,
I'd probably be dead right now.
You really saved me there.
Thanks, Dad.
Father?
Father...
No...
...
It isn't...
No...
No.
You must be tired.
You did everything you could.
So leave the rest to me.
Maybe she is truly gone.
Lady Zenith!
Good morning, my lady.
You're safe now.
Hey, Mom.
My lady, it's Master Rudeus.
Nearly ten years have passed since you last saw him.
Could it be that my lady?
Ray?
Hi.
You're dead.
Why?
Wow.
You